[
    {
        "question": "Where do you go to buy zombies?",
        "answer": "The monSTORE!",
        "punchline": [
            "monSTORE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the man say to his forgetful zombie wife?",
        "answer": "You forgot your HEAD because it wasn't attached!",
        "punchline": [
            "HEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did the zombie take out for dinner?",
        "answer": "His GHOULfriend!",
        "punchline": [
            "GHOULfriend"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie ignore all his new Facebook friends?",
        "answer": "He was still DIGESTING all his old Facebook friends!",
        "punchline": [
            "DIGESTING"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie's favorite toy?",
        "answer": "A DEADY bear!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEADY"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did everyone say about the big zombie party?",
        "answer": "It was DEAD & full of STIFFS!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD",
            "STIFFS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say to his date?",
        "answer": "I just love a woman with BRAAAINS!",
        "punchline": [
            "BRAAAINS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the zombie's greatest invention?",
        "answer": "Canned BRAAAINS!",
        "punchline": [
            "BRAAAINS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between zombies & patched jeans?",
        "answer": "Zombies are DEAD men, jeans are menDEAD!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD",
            "menDEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do all the Apple zombies keep telling Steve Jobs?",
        "answer": "We're DYING to have YOU for dinner!",
        "punchline": [
            "DYING",
            "YOU"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the zombie's \"Grease\" audition go?",
        "answer": "Bad, they couldn't envision Danny as GREEN, ROTTING & GRUESOME!",
        "punchline": [
            "GREEN,",
            "ROTTING",
            "GRUESOME"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie hope for before his blind date?",
        "answer": "Someone with a PULSE & plenty of BRAAAINS!",
        "punchline": [
            "PULSE",
            "BRAAAINS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie call his new dating handbook?",
        "answer": "\"DYING To Meet You!\"",
        "punchline": [
            "\"DYING"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why didn't the zombie get the job?",
        "answer": "They wanted someone with more energy & less ROTTING flesh!",
        "punchline": [
            "ROTTING"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the zombie treat every day of death?",
        "answer": "Like he was LIVING!",
        "punchline": [
            "LIVING"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie buy a Jet Ski?",
        "answer": "He wanted to ENJOY the apocalypse!",
        "punchline": [
            "ENJOY"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a zombie with lots of kids?",
        "answer": "A MOMster!",
        "punchline": [
            "MOMster"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of candy do zombies refuse to eat?",
        "answer": "LIFE Savers!",
        "punchline": [
            "LIFE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie's friend say after she joined Greenpeace?",
        "answer": "Uggghhh, you're one of those annoying GREEN zombies!",
        "punchline": [
            "GREEN"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a zombie door-to-door salesman?",
        "answer": "A DEAD ringer!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do zombies go swimming?",
        "answer": "The DEAD Sea!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do most zombies live?",
        "answer": "On DEAD end streets!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the safest place in your home from a zombie?",
        "answer": "The LIVING room!",
        "punchline": [
            "LIVING"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the zombie war?",
        "answer": "Nobody, it was a DEAD tie!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie's ex say when she wouldn't stop calling?",
        "answer": "You're DEAD to me!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a dead bee?",
        "answer": "A zomBEE!",
        "punchline": [
            "zomBEE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do zombies eat dinner with their family?",
        "answer": "No, their family IS the dinner!",
        "punchline": [
            "IS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say before his fight?",
        "answer": "Do you want a PIECE of me?",
        "punchline": [
            "PIECE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do dark circles around the zombie's eyes make him look dead?",
        "answer": "No, but being DEAD does!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie go crazy?",
        "answer": "He had LOST his mind!",
        "punchline": [
            "LOST"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie's favorite meal?",
        "answer": "A MANwich!",
        "punchline": [
            "MANwich"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say after seeing his neighbor's new car?",
        "answer": "I'm GREEN with envy!",
        "punchline": [
            "GREEN"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say to his wife Barbara?",
        "answer": "I'm coming to get you, BARBARA!",
        "punchline": [
            "BARBARA"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How are zombies like computers?",
        "answer": "They use megaBITES!",
        "punchline": [
            "megaBITES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you know a zombie is tired?",
        "answer": "He's DEAD on his feet!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie do after he dumped his girlfriend?",
        "answer": "He wiped his BUTT!",
        "punchline": [
            "BUTT"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie's favorite shampoo?",
        "answer": "Head & Shoulders!",
        "punchline": []
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of streets do zombies like best?",
        "answer": "DEAD end!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEAD"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does a zombie get when he comes home late for dinner?",
        "answer": "The cold SHOULDER!",
        "punchline": [
            "SHOULDER"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie eat after his teeth were pulled?",
        "answer": "The DENTIST!",
        "punchline": [
            "DENTIST"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do zombies go on cruises?",
        "answer": "The DEADiterranean Sea!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEADiterranean"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do zombies wear when it's raining?",
        "answer": "BRAAAINcoats!",
        "punchline": [
            "BRAAAINcoats"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do zombies eat candy with their fingers?",
        "answer": "No, they EAT the FINGERS separately!",
        "punchline": [
            "EAT",
            "FINGERS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie cross the road?",
        "answer": "To get to the BRAAAINS!",
        "punchline": [
            "BRAAAINS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Knock...knock! Who's there? Zombie! Zombie who?",
        "answer": "BRAAAINS!",
        "punchline": [
            "BRAAAINS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How do they smooth the ice on a zombie hockey rink?",
        "answer": "With a ZomBONI!",
        "punchline": [
            "ZomBONI"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does it take to become a zombie?",
        "answer": "DEADication!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEADication"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do zombies order at bars?",
        "answer": "A shot of To-KILL-Ya!",
        "punchline": [
            "To-KILL-Ya"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you hear about the zombie who tortured his victims with music?",
        "answer": "His BACH was worse than his bite!",
        "punchline": [
            "BACH"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What time do zombies wake up?",
        "answer": "At ATE o'clock!",
        "punchline": [
            "ATE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie's favorite TV show?",
        "answer": "\"CHOMPING On The Stars!\"",
        "punchline": [
            "\"CHOMPING"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How do zombies serve their country?",
        "answer": "In the Marine CORPSE!",
        "punchline": [
            "CORPSE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What cereal does a zombie eat for breakfast?",
        "answer": "Raisin BRAAAINS!",
        "punchline": [
            "BRAAAINS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do zombies eat popcorn with their fingers?",
        "answer": "No, they EAT the FINGERS separately!",
        "punchline": [
            "EAT",
            "FINGERS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why do zombies make good DJs?",
        "answer": "They produce lots of sound BITES!",
        "punchline": [
            "BITES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie go to the hospital?",
        "answer": "He wanted to learn some SICK jokes!",
        "punchline": [
            "SICK"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie lose his lawsuit?",
        "answer": "He had NO LEG to STAND ON!",
        "punchline": [
            "NO",
            "LEG",
            "STAND",
            "ON"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you do if you see a zombie?",
        "answer": "Hope it's HALLOWEEN!",
        "punchline": [
            "HALLOWEEN"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did one zombie say to the other zombie while eating a comedian?",
        "answer": "This tastes FUNNY!",
        "punchline": [
            "FUNNY"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do vegetarian zombies crave?",
        "answer": "GRAAAINS...more GRAAAAAAINS!",
        "punchline": [
            "GRAAAINS...more",
            "GRAAAAAAINS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do little zombies play?",
        "answer": "CORPSES & Robbers!",
        "punchline": [
            "CORPSES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie's friend say when introduced to his new girlfriend?",
        "answer": "Where the heck did you DIG her UP from?",
        "punchline": [
            "DIG",
            "UP"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who do cowboy zombies fight?",
        "answer": "DEADskins!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEADskins"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What has a dog's head, a cat's tail & brains all over its face?",
        "answer": "A zombie LEAVING the PET STORE!",
        "punchline": [
            "LEAVING",
            "PET",
            "STORE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is black, white & dead all over?",
        "answer": "A zombie in a TUXEDO!",
        "punchline": [
            "TUXEDO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie cross the road?",
        "answer": "He wanted to EAT the chicken!",
        "punchline": [
            "EAT"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you hear about the zombie who was expelled from school?",
        "answer": "He kept BUTTERING up his teacher!",
        "punchline": [
            "BUTTERING"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie stop teaching?",
        "answer": "He only had one PUPIL!",
        "punchline": [
            "PUPIL"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How do zombies tell their future?",
        "answer": "With their HORRORscope!",
        "punchline": [
            "HORRORscope"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do zombies like to eat at cookouts?",
        "answer": "Beanie HALLOWEENies!",
        "punchline": [
            "HALLOWEENies"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie go to the orthodontist?",
        "answer": "To improve his BITE!",
        "punchline": [
            "BITE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many zombies does it take to screw in a light bulb?",
        "answer": "None, zombies CAN'T FIT in a light bulb & they DON'T screw!",
        "punchline": [
            "CAN'T",
            "FIT",
            "DON'T"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie put poison in people's corn flakes?",
        "answer": "He was a CEREAL killer!",
        "punchline": [
            "CEREAL"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you get when you cross a zombie with a snowman?",
        "answer": "FrostBITE!",
        "punchline": [
            "FrostBITE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie's favorite mode of transportation?",
        "answer": "SCAREplanes!",
        "punchline": [
            "SCAREplanes"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of dogs do zombies like best?",
        "answer": "BLOODhound!",
        "punchline": [
            "BLOODhound"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the dyslexic zombie starve to death?",
        "answer": "He couldn't find any SNIAAARB!",
        "punchline": [
            "SNIAAARB"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why was the zombie afraid to cross the road?",
        "answer": "He had LOST his GUTS!",
        "punchline": [
            "LOST",
            "GUTS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie's favorite football team?",
        "answer": "The Washington DEADskins!",
        "punchline": [
            "DEADskins"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How do zombies keep their hair in place?",
        "answer": "With SCARE spray!",
        "punchline": [
            "SCARE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is black, white & red all over?",
        "answer": "A nun being EATEN by zombies!",
        "punchline": [
            "EATEN"
        ]
    }
]